
Changelog 2
-----------
   -NK-

Continious entries.
Newest placed first.


>>> All errors from 'Changelist 1' fixed, staring new Changelog <<<
	---------------------------------------------------
	>>Note: As compiling of entities is done,
	this changelist will detail the creation
	and making of cheatures/beasts/pops
	Languages are still postponed.		<<


#######
Changelists and logs marked as following under.
-------
(x) is fixed/removed bug/completed
(>) is forwarded
(>>) is postponed
(#) is currently worked on
(¤) is on wait, pending work on parent item
Entries marked with * has note at end string.
########


NOTE, 13.07.16
--------------

x   -Making 'Noekk', evil horse creature for evil entities.
    x   -Needs to replace some tissue with 'Dank Matter'.
#   -Work on snakes/ormer.
    ¤   -Work on 'Eldorm' postponed until 'Noekk' is done.


NOTE, 08.07.16
--------------

#	-Worked on file for snakes/ormer.
	x	-Created creature 'staalorm'.
	x	-Edited local tissue 'steel'. Removed flesh tags, made more solid and
		 added relative thickness. Works for scale and teeth now.
	#	-Started working on 'Eldorm', a giant orm with fireball as attack.


NOTE, 07.07.16
--------------

x	-Start work on a giant snake inspired by gjormundgandr, still unnamed.
		*Work started, see separate bulletpoint.
#	-Started file for snakes/ormer.
	x	-Buildt standard, "snok", to use as template for giant orms
	x	-Buildt Ovorm, a giant orm.
	#	-Started working on 'Staalorm', a giant orm with steel scales.


NOTE, 06.07.16
--------------

x	-Started work on creature 'Tusse'.
	x	*Make cave pop, needs work on entity file. Creature file done for now.
	x	*Make item 'pads' or the like for small pieces of lether armor.
	x	*Rakes(changed to pitchfork) and spades(used existing 'skovl', renamed) need to be made for creature. Known for stealing tools in folklore.
	x	*Make 'Hulder' as a savage version of 'Tusse'.
x	-Start work on a mischeivous 'nisse', still unnamed.
	x	*Named 'Rampenisse'.
#	-Start work on a giant snake inspired by gjormundgandr, still unnamed.

x	-Changed some tokens in Tusse Entity file.


NOTE, 05.07.16
--------------

#	-Started work on creature 'Tusse'.
	#	*Make cave pop, needs work on entity file. Creature file done for now.
	¤	*Make item 'pads' or the like for small pieces of lether armor.
	¤	*Rakes and spades need to be made for creature. Known for stealing tools in folklore.
	¤	*Make 'Hulder' as a savage version of 'Tusse'.
	-Start work on a mischeivous 'nisse', still unnamed.
	-Start work on a giant snake inspired by gjormundgandr, still unnamed.